{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Rabbits can see what's behind themselves without turning their heads.",
      "correct_answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "The ghosts in 'Pac-Man' and 'Ms. Pac-Man' have completely different behavior.",
      "correct_answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first 'Metal Gear' game was released for the PlayStation 1.",
      "correct_answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Faust is a playable character in 'Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator'.",
      "correct_answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Valve's 'Portal' and 'Half-Life' franchises exist within the same in-game universe.",
      "correct_answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Time on Computers is measured via the EPOX System.",
      "correct_answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.",
      "correct_answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.",
      "correct_answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Heroes of the Storm, the Cursed Hollow map gimmick requires players to kill the undead to curse the enemy team.",
      "correct_answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney's 1940's film Fantasia.",
      "correct_answer": "True"
    }
  ]
}
